Guide to the George Good papers, 1928-1998.
Good, George papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
George Good papers, 1928-1998.
21-25-3493
George Good
1.2 cubic ft.
Correspondence, Manuscripts, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, course material, publications and minutes of meetings of the New York State Nurserymen's Association (1928-1969) and the New York State Arborists Association (1965-1969)..
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Emeritus professor of Ornamental Horticulture, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, course material, publications and minutes of meetings of the New York State Nurserymen's Association (1928-1969) and the New York State Arborists Association (1965-1969)..
SUBJECTS
Names:
Good, George; Cornell University--Faculty.; New York State Arborists Association.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Students.; New York State College of Agriculture.Dept. of Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture.; New York State Nurserymen's Association.
Subjects:
Floriculture--Study and teaching.; Horticulture--Study and teaching.; Botany.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Corresponedence- "E", 1980s (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Corresponedence- "F", 1980S (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Corresponedence- "G", 1980s (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Corresponedence- "H", 1980s (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
  - Corresponedence- "I-J", 1980s (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Corresponedence- "K", 1980s (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Corresponedence- "L", 1980s (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Corresponedence- "M", 1980s (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Corresponedence- "N", 1980s (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Corresponedence- "O", 1980s (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Corresponedence- "P", 1980s (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Corresponedence- "Q-R", 1980s (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Corresponedence- "S", 1980s (Box 1, Folder 14-16)
  - Corresponedence- "T", 1980-1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Corresponedence- "U-V", 1980-1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Corresponedence- "W", 1980-1990 (Box 1, Folder 19-20)
  - Corresponedence- "X-Z", 1980-1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Series II: Seminars / Workshops
  - Ornamental Horticulture Seminar, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Cornell Landscape Design Seminar- Workshop, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Ornamental Horticulture Businessmen's Seminar, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Landscape Design Seminar Workshop, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Ornamental Horticulture Businessmen's Seminar, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cornell Landscape Design Seminar Workshop, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Ornamental Horticulture Businessmen's Seminar, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ornamental Horticulture Businessmen's Seminar, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Nursery Work Group Newsletter, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Series III: Course Material
  - Master Gardner: Plant Physiology, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Garden Center Inventory (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Floriculture 317, Fall 1974; 1978; 1981 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Floriculture 317, Fall 1982, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Floriculture 421, Fall 1984 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Floriculture 421, Fall 1986 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Floriculture 421, Fall 1987 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Series IV: Committees / Associations
  - Plant Science Curriculum Committee, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Plant Science Collections Committee, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - NYS Arborists Association, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - NYS Nurserymen's Association, 1928-1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - NYS Nurserymen's Association, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - NYS Arborists Association, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - NYS Arborists Association- correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - NYS Arborists Association- Training Course, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - NYS Arborists Association- conference, Jan. 1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Series V: Research / Publications
  - Papers and Articles by George Good (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Trees and Shrubs Bulletin- photos, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Ornamental Horticulture Research Program, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Nursery Research, 1956-1967 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - "Review of the Doctoral Program in the Dept. of Horticulture at Mississippi State University" by George Good (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1 volume listing attendees to the annual New York State Nurseryman's Association Conference, December 15, 1930 - August 15, 1946., 1930-1946 (Box 3)